# **GRANT SCRIVER**

4503 Lakeview Drive, Edina, Minnesota 55424 • (612) 875-0809 • grantscriver@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://grantscriver.github.io/React-Portfolio
GitHub: https://github.com/grantscriver

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/grant-scriver/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/grant-scriver/</a>

# **Professional Summary**

With over 5 years of work experience in the service and manufacturing industries, ready to deploy technical skills in HTML, CSS and JavaScript as a front-end or back-end developer contributing to the success of a cutting edge, entrepreneurial organization.

## **Technical Skills:**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript Databases: MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB

Tools: VS Code, Git, GitHub Pages, Heroku, Node, various APIs

Libraries: React, jQuery, Bootstrap,

## Major projects:

## **React Personal Portfolio application:**

Description: React application with React-router to navigate through my portfolio webpage Technologies used: React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React-Router. Bootstrap, Mobile first design GitHub Live Site

### **Budget Tracker application:**

Description: Online / Offline application for keeping track of budget expenses Technologies used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MongoDB, Mongoose, IndexedDB GitHub Live Site

### **Work History:**

**Assembly Technician,** 9/2019 to 3/2020 **Entrust Datacard** – Shakopee, MN

- Data-driven assembly of card printers using parts and document interpretation.
- Component programming of assembly machinery

#### Assembly Technician, 9/2018 to 9/2019

**Graco Inc.** – Minneapolis, MN

- Data-driven assembly of various industrial power tool products in a factory setting
- Testing products for defects and flaws that may have occurred during assembly

### Various Service Industry Positions, 10/2013 to 09/2018

- Trejo's Tacos Cashier Los Angeles, CA
- Domino's Pizza Delivery Driver Los Angeles, CA
- Pizza Luce Delivery Driver Hopkins, MN

#### **Education:**

- University of Minnesota: Full Stack Developer Certificate, December 2020
- Edina High School: High School Diploma, May 2014